A Finding Aid to the Fischbach Gallery Records, 1937-2015, bulk 1963-1977, in the Archives of American Art AAA.fiscgall
Archives of American Art
Fischbach Gallery records
bulk 1963-1977
1937-2015
AAA.fiscgall
Archives of American Art
39.3 Linear feet
The records of New York City Fischbach Gallery measure 39.3 linear feet and date from 1937 to 2015 with the bulk of materials dating from 1963 to 1977. The majority of the collection consists of artists files containing a wide variety of materials documenting the gallery's relationship with its stable of modern and avant garde artists, as well as gallery exhibitions. Files include biographical materials, correspondence, printed materials, and photographs. Gallery records also include general business correspondence, access-restricted financial records; and additional printed materials. The 2015 addition of 14 linear feet consists of inventory and client sales records in the form of card indexes.
Fischbach Gallery
Provenance
Gallery founder Marilyn C. Fischbach and director A. Aladar Marberger donated the majority of the Fischbach Gallery records in 1978. Additional records were donated in 2001 by Maureen Dawley on behalf of the Carnegie Mellon University. In 2015, Lawrence di Carlo, Director of Fischbach Gallery donated an additional 14 linear feet of records.
Restrictions on Access
Use of original papers requires an appointment. Written permission from the donor is also required to view the series of financial records. Contact the Reference Services Department for more information.
Historical Note
The Fischbach Gallery was founded in 1960 by Marilyn Cole Fischbach at 799 Madison Avenue in New York City. The gallery was noted for its stable of minimalist young artists in the 1960s, and the work of the painterly realists in the 1970s. The gallery remains open today.
During its early years, the gallery was among the first to focus on 1960s avant-garde and minimalist artists. Marilyn possessed a talent for discovering young artists and for helping them advance their careers. Many of these young artists became well-known including Ronald Bladen, Eva Hesse, and Alex Katz. Other artists represented by the gallery include Allan D'Arcangelo, Les Levine, Robert Mangold, Robert Ryman, George Sugarman, and Robert Swain.
The gallery also had an active exhibition schedule and organized and hosted group exhibitions of modern art including "According to the Letter" (1963), "Hard Center" (1963), and "Direct Representation" (1969). Additionally, the Fishbach Gallery hosted "Eccentric Abstraction" in 1966, an exhibition organized by Lucy Lippard.
Later, the gallery moved to W. 57th Street in Manhattan. Fischbach hired A. Aladar Marberger as director of the gallery. Under his direction, the Fischbach Gallery shifted from the avant-garde to contemporary American realism and minimalist sculpture. In the 1980s, Marilyn Fischbach brought three investors into the gallery. She remined a co-owner, but lived in Paris, France for many years prior to her death at the age of seventy-two. The Fischbach Gallery remains open at 210 West 11th Street at 25th Street in New York City.
Scope and Content Note
The records of New York City Fischbach Gallery measure 39.3 linear feet and date from 1937 to 2015 with the bulk of materials dating from 1963 to 1977. The majority of the collection consists of artists files containing a wide variety of materials documenting the gallery's relationship with its stable of modern and avant garde artists, as well as gallery exhibitions. Files include biographical materials, correspondence, printed materials, and photographs. Gallery records also include general business correspondence, access-restricted financial records; and additional printed materials.
Artists and Exhibition Files contain information on over one hundred Fischbach Gallery artists and measure 18 linear feet. The contents of each file varies, but typically may include biographical information; correspondence between the artist, museums, and other galleries; scattered consignment information; printed materials including articles, clippings, exhibition announcements and catalogs, and press releases; photographs of the artist, installations, constructions, and works of art; and negatives, slides, and transparencies. Substantial files are found for John Altoon, Stephen Antonakos, Ronald Bladen, Wynn Chamberlain, Allan D'Arcangelo, Gene Davis, Anne Dunn, Piero Gilardi, Eva Hesse, Alex Katz, Nicholas Krushenick, Les Levine, Robert Mangold, Doug Ohlson, Anne Ryan, Robert Ryman, Arlene Slavin, Tony Smith, George Sugarman, and Robert Swain, among others. Also included are files pertaining to group exhibitions including "According to the Letter" (1963), "Hard Center" (1963), "Six Women" (1965), "Game Without Rules" (1966), "Direct Representation" (1969), and "Eccentric Abstraction" (1966) which was organized by Lucy Lippard.
General gallery correspondence is business correspondence between the gallery and companies, individuals, museums, galleries, dealers, new or non-Fischbach artists, and institutions. Additional business records consist of an address book, lists of Fischbach artists, gallery plans, a notebook, as well as guest lists, mailing lists, and press lists.
Financial records are access restricted and require written permission from the donor's representative for use. The files document financial transactions for many of the artists represented in the artists files and includes sales records, invoices, artists' payments, and correspondence about sales and possible sales. The alphabetical financial files document routine gallery business, such as framing, shipping, insurance, messenger, publicity, etc. and are organized by name of business. General financial files consist of accounting ledgers, banking documents, insurance claims, and travel accounts.
Printed materials consist of various business cards, clippings concerning the Fischbach Gallery, and a pamphlet by Ron Williams as a guide to New York galleries. The bulk of printed materials are found in the Artists and Exhibition Files.
A small series of photographs include those from the Thiabaut Gallery, and unidentified photos of landscapes. It is likely that Fischbach Gallery occupied the space previously used by the Thiabaut Gallery and some materials were included in the collection for that reason. The bulk of photographic materials are found in the Artists and Exhibition Files.
In 2015, 14 feet of records were added to the collection. The addition consists of inventory and client sales records in the form of card indexes.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged as 7 series.
Series 1: Artists and Exhibitions Files, 1937-1977 (Boxes 1-18, 28; 18 linear feet)
Series 2: Gallery Correspondence, 1962-1974 (Boxes 18-19; 1.75 linear feet)
Series 3: Business Records, 1969-1971 (Box 27; 0.3 linear feet)
Series 4: Financial Records, 1963-1975 (Boxes 20-25; 4.5 linear feet)
Series 5: Printed Material, 1963-1972 (Box 26; 6 folders)
Series 6: Photographs, circa 1960s (Box 26; 2 folders)
Series 7: Addition to the Fischbach Gallery Records, circa 1960s-2015 (Box 29-42; 14 linear feet)
Altoon, John, 1925-; Antonakos, Stephen, 1926-2013; Bladen, Ronald, 1918-1988; Chamberlain, Wynn; D'Arcangelo, Allan, 1930-; Davis, Gene, 1920-1985; Dunn, Anne; Gilardi, Piero, 1942-; Hesse, Eva, 1936-1970; Katz, Alex, 1927-; Krushenick, Nicholas, 1929-1999; Levine, Les, 1935-; Mangold, Robert, 1937-; Ohlson, Douglas Dean, 1936-; Ryan, Anne, 1889-1954; Ryman, Robert, 1930-; Slavin, Arlene, 1942-; Smith, Tony, 1912-; Sugarman, George, 1912-1999; Swain, Robert, 1940-; Thiabaut Galley; Art galleries, Commercial--New York (State)--New York; Art, American; Art, Modern--20th century--United States; Artists--United States; Gallery records; Minimal art--United States; Photographs
- Artists and Exhibitions Files, 1937-1977; Series 1; (Boxes 1-18, 28; 18 linear feet)
  Scope and Contents note
  Artists and exhibitions files are found for over one hundred artists either represented by the gallery or exhibiting with the gallery. Files contain a wide variety of materials, and the extent and type vary for each artist. Typically files contain biographical information; correspondence between the artist, museums, and other galleries; scattered consignment and loan information; printed materials including articles, clippings, exhibition announcements and catalogs, and press releases; photographs of the artist, installations, constructions, and works of art; and negatives, slides, and transparencies. Substantial artist files are found for John Altoon, Anne Arnold, Ronald Bladen, George Brecht, Wynn Chamberlain, Allan D'Arcangelo, Gene Davis, Robert Grosvenor, Ira Joel Haber, Eva Hesse, Yvonne Jacquette, Alex Katz, Les Levine, Robert Mangold, Doug Ohlson, Ray Parker, Anne Ryan, Robert Ryman, Tony Smith, and George Sugarman. Of special note are photos of portraits by Alex Katz depicting his friends including Richard Bellamy, Edwin Denby, Al Held, Elaine de Kooning, and Neil Welliver.
  Also included are files pertaining to group exhibitions either organized or hosted by the gallery, including "According to the Letter" (1963), "Hard Center" (1963), "Six Women" (1965), "Game Without Rules" (1966), "Direct Representation" (1969), and "Eccentric Abstraction" (1966) which was organized by Lucy Lippard.
  Arrangement note
  Artists Files are arranged alphabetically by artist and further divided by types of materials. Correspondence is in rough chronological order due to previous arrangements made by the Fischbach Gallery.
  Materials relating to financial transactions including sales and payment are found in Series 4: Financial Records, which are access restrited.
  - Aach, Herb (Box 1)
    - Biographical Information, 1965 February (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Altoon, John (Box 1)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Photos of the Artist, circa 1966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Photos of Installations, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Anthony, William (Box 1)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Antonakos, Stephen (Box 1)
    - Biographical Information, 1965-1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Artist's Copy of Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Brocton Art Center Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - General Correspondence, 1968-1971; (4 folders) (Box 1, Folder 13-16)
    - Heath and Company Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1968-1971; (4 folders) (Box 1, Folder 18-21)
    - Consignment and Loan Information, 1967-1971 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1966-1971; (2 folders) (Box 1, Folder 23-24)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1967-1971; (3 folders) (Box 1, Folder 25-27)
    - Press Releases, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Installation Instructions, 1967 January (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Photos of the Artist, circa 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Photos of Construction of Works of Art, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Photos of Installations, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1965-1970; (2 folders) (Box 1, Folder 33-34)
    - Transparencies and Negatives of Works of Art, circa 1960s (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Slides of Works of Art, 1965-1969 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Arnold, Anne (Box 2)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1965 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Artist's Copy of Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence, 1964-1971; (2 folders) (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1965-1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Consignment and Loan Information, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1960-1969 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Lists of Works of Art, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Baer, Jo (Box 2)
    - Photos of the Artist and Works of Art, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Baynard, Ed (Box 2)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Bechtle, Robert (Box 2)
    - Biographical Information, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Bennett, John (Box 2)
    - Biographical Information, 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - General Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Consignment and Loan Information, 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1965-1971 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1965-1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Photos of Installations, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1965-1968 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Slides and Negatives of Works of Art, circa 1967 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Bishop, James (Box 2)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1968-1972 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - General Correspondence, 1968-1972 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1968-1972 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Consignment and Loan Information, 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1965-1972 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1965-1972 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Photos of Installations, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1965-1970 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Negatives of Works of Art, circa 1970s (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Bladen, Ronald (Box 2)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1965 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Artist's Copy of Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - "Cathedral Evening" Correspondence, 1969-1976 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - General Correspondence, 1965-1977; (2 folders) (Box 2, Folder 37-38)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1968-1971; (4 folders) (Box 2, Folder 39-42)
    - Consignment and Loan Information, 1968-1975 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Gallery Plans and Instructions, circa 1969 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1966-1976; (3 folders) (Box 2, Folder 45-47)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1966-1976; (5 folders) (Box 3, Folder 1-5)
    - Press Releases, 1967, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Photos of the Artist, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Photos of Construction of Works of Art, 1967-1971 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Photos of Installations, 1966-1973; (4 folders) (Box 3, Folder 9-12)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1965-1975; (3 folders) (Box 3, Folder 13-15)
    - Negatives of Works of Art, circa 1971 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Bosson, Jack (Box 3)
    - General Correspondence, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Brainard, Joe (Box 3)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1971 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - General Corresopndence, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Articles and Clippings, circa 1975 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Brecht, George (Box 3)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1967 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - General Correspondence, 1959, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1965-1971; (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 25-26)
    - Theft Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Consignment and Loan Information, 1966-1972 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1965-1971 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1965-1971 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Press Releases, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1966-1969 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Negatives of Works of Art, circa 1966 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Carpogrossi, Guiseppe (Box 3)
    - Photos of Works of Art, circa 1950 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Carsman, Jon (Box 3)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Carswell, John (Box 3)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1965 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - General Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Chamberlain, Wynn (Box 3)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1965 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - General Correspondence, circa 1965 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Press Releases, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Negatives and Slides of Works of Art, circa 1964 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Chryssa (Box 4)
    - Photos of Works of Art, circa 1960s (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Civitico, Bruno (Box 4)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1970 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - D'Arcangelo, Allan (Box 4)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1970 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence, 1963-1969; (3 folders) (Box 4, Folder 7-9)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1968-1969; (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 10-11)
    - Consignment and Loan Information, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1963-1969; (3 folders) (Box 4, Folder 13-15)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1963-1968; (9 folders) (Box 4, Folder 16-24)
    - Press Releases, 1963-1968 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Photos of the Artist, circa 1965 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Photos of Installations, circa 1966 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1963-1969; (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 4-5)
    - Negatives and Transparencies of Works of Art, circa 1960s; (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 6-7)
  - Daniel, Mell (Box 5)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1970 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - General Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Negatives of Works of Art, circa 1970 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Dash, Robert (Box 5)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1971-1976 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Negatives and Transparencies of Works of Art, circa 1970s (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Davis, Gene (Box 5)
    - Artist's Copy of Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - General Correspondence, 1968-1970; (3 folders) (Box 5, Folder 16-18)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1968-1971; (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 19-20)
    - Consignment and Loan Information, 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Photos of the Artist, circa 1970s (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Photos of Installations, 1968-1972 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Photos of Installations--"Micro Paintings", 1969 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1965-1976; (3 folders) (Box 5, Folder 25-27)
    - Negatives of Works of Art, circa 1960s; (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 28-29)
  - Dibbets, Jan (Box 5)
    - Photos of Works of Art, circa 1960s (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Negatives of Works of Art, circa 1960s (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Dodd, Lois (Box 5)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Drummond, Sally (Box 5)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1965-1967 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - General Correspondence, 1965, 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1967-1971 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Consignment and Loan Information, 1966-1970 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1962-1969 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1962-1969 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Dunn, Anne (Box 5)
    - General Correspondence, 1965-1971 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Consignment and Loan Information, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1966-1972 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Ellenberg, Mark (Box 5)
    - Photos of Works of Art, circa 1960s (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Filco, Stanley (Box 5)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Flanagan, Barry (Box 5)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1970 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - General Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Consignment and Loan Information, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1967-1971 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1967-1971; (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 2-3)
    - Press Releases, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Installation Materials, circa 1960s (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Photos of Installations, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1965-1969; (4 folders) (Box 6, Folder 7-10)
    - Negatives of Works of Art, circa 1960s (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Flavin, Dan (Box 6)
    - Photos of Works of Art, circa 1960s (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Fontana, Lucio (Box 6)
    - General Correspondence, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Frazier, Paul (Box 6)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1965-1967 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - General Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Photos of Installations, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1964-1969 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Transparencies of Works of Art, circa 1960s (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Friedberg, Richard (Box 6)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1973 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Photos of Installations and Works of Art, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Slides of Works of Art, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Georges, Paul (Box 6)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Slides and Transparencies of Works of Art, circa 1970s (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Gianakos, Stylianos (Box 6)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1968 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - General Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Consignment and Loan Information, 1968-1970 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Photos of the Artist, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Photos of Installations, 1968 September (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1967-1969; (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 36-37)
    - Negatives of Works of Art, circa 1968 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Gilardi, Piero (Box 6)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1968 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - General Correspondence, 1967-1970; (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 40-41)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Consignment and Loan Information, 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Leonardo Interview, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Press Releases, circa 1967 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Photos of Installations, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1966-1968; (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 8-9)
    - Negatives, Slides, and Transparencies of Works of Art, circa 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Giorno, J. (Box 7)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Goodman, Jerome (Box 7)
    - Photos of Works of Art, circa 1960s (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Gorchov, Ron (Box 7)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1972-1974; (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 13-14)
    - Slides of Works of Art, circa 1973 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Gorski, Daniel (Box 7)